http://www.apollosafety.com/privacy-policy

Dec 3rd
Twenty-one years ago today, a blaze at the Worcester Cold Storage and Warehouse Co. claimed the live...
Nov 11th
Thank you, Veterans for your sacrifice.
Thank you, especially, to our President and CEO @johnvcarval...
Nov 4th
Apollo Safety has been fortunate to serve our community for 25 years! As a veteran-owned business we...
Aug 13th
Major issue with Comcast this morning - no internet - or email. Phones working - call 800-813-5408 t...
Jul 13th
Potentially toxic sanitizer being recalled - Apollo has alternative solution - Alcohol Free
Register
Login
View Cart
(0 Items)
800-813-5408
Ventis® GarageLone Worker DevicesCareersNewsroomGas MonitorsBlogContact UsOffice LocatorTestimonialsGalleryReturn Policy
Browse Store
Health & WellnessSingle Gas Monitors - PortableMulti-Gas Monitors - PortableFixed - Station Gas MonitorsGas Monitor AccessoriesCalibration GasesJob Site Safety EquipmentApollo Safety Rental CenterGas Monitor Calibration and RepairReplacement SensorsRental EquipmentApollo Safety Refurbished and Demo Gas MonitorsMade in the USAProtective Workwear and ClothingJanitorial and SanitationGas Monitor PartsFall Protection GearGas Detection TubesPreownedAdhesives, Sealants and TapesNEW!!
Apollo Safety
Ventis® GarageLone Worker DevicesCareersNewsroomGas MonitorsBlogContact UsOffice LocatorTestimonialsGalleryReturn Policy
Request Catalog
Mailing List
Sign up for our newsletter
Contact Us
Apollo Safety
57 Walnut St
Fall River, MA 02720508-673-2544
HomePrivacy PolicyPrivacy Policy
This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this Web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through this Web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the collection, use and distribution of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control.
How you can update or correct any inaccuracies in your information.
Information Collection, Use and SharingWe request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we'll use this information to contact you.
The personal information you provide us may be shared with third parties. This information may be combined with other personally identifiable information, such as demographics, available from our records. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. It may also be used by our marketing partners to bring you offers of interest. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with our marketing partners, please contact us via email.
We use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.
Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet.
We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on your past visits to this website.
We along with third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our site.
We use data from Google's Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) with Google Analytics.
Your Access to and Control Over InformationIf you subscribe to our mailing list, you may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by contacting us via email. You can also do the following:
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the Web site, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information, such as credit card data, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your Web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the Web page.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
Learn more about Opting Out
Google Analytics Opt Out Info
Google Ad Settings
© 2020 Copyright Apollo Safety. All Rights Reserved.
Ventis® GarageLone Worker DevicesCareersNewsroomGas MonitorsBlogContact UsOffice LocatorTestimonialsGalleryReturn Policy About
